Bobbie Ysabel Benedito UX Designer

bobbieysabel.com
Github
LinkedIn
b.y.benedito@gmail.com
(914)327-6160

About

I'm a New York based **UX Designer** with a background in nanomaterials engineering and computer science. I apply my education in building physical products to designing digital solutions.

Skills

UX/UI design
Interaction design
Information architecture
Wireframing and prototyping
UX documentation
User stories and user flows
User research
Competitive analysis
Usability testing

Tools

Figma

Sketch

InVision

HTML/CSS

JavaScript

AutoCAD

Projects

Jumpstart | Web App Prototype

A web app that helps users bridge gaps in their career knowledge. Utilizes a chatbot to recommend relevant career development resources to users. Built in Figma.

Wardrobe | iOS Prototype

A mobile app that encourages users to be more intentional about their clothing. Users can track their clothes in a virtual closet, create new outfits, and save style inspiration. Built in Figma.

Experience

Research Associate | SUNY Polytechnic Institute

Aug 2017-Apr 2018, Albany, NY

- Conducted research to develop Microfluidic Intravital Window (MFIW), a device used to collect and image cancer cells
- Drafted 2D designs of device components in AutoCAD
- Designed and ran experiments to characterize materials

Research Associate | SUNY Polytechnic Institute

Jun 2015-Aug 2015, Albany, NY

- Conducted research to develop the NAno IntraVital Device (NANIVID), a diagnostic device used to collect cancer cells
- Modeled the device using 3D drafting software AutoCAD
- Gained experience working with a team in a lab environment

Education

University at Albany, SUNY

2014-2018

B.S. in Nanomaterials Engineering and Minor in Computer Science

Bloc

2018-2019

UX/UI Design